<resources>
    <string name="app_name">newpaper_assign_2</string>

    <string-array name="title">
        <item>Humane is looking for a buyer after the AI Pin’s underwhelming debut</item>
        <item>Microsoft’s big bet on building a new type of AI computer</item>
        <item>The Sonos Ace headphones are here, and they’re damn impressive</item>
        <item>Google’s AI search results are already getting ads</item>
        <item>Square Enix will let Kingdom Hearts cook on Steam</item>
        <item>Apple needs to explain that bug that resurfaced deleted photos</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="body">
        <item>"Humane, the startup behind the poorly-reviewed AI Pin wearable computer, is already hunting for a potential buyer for its business. That’s according to a report from Bloomberg, which says the company — led by former longtime Apple employees Imran Chaudhri and Bethany Bongiorno — is “seeking a price of between $750 million and $1 billion.”Humane developed its own operating system called CosmOS that runs on the AI Pin. It hooks into a network of AI models to fetch answers for voice queries and to analyze what the built-in camera is pointed at. For some interactions, the device beams out a laser “display” that is projected onto the wearer’s inner palm.
            \n A monthly subscription is required to keep the device active.The Bloomberg report notes that Humane has raised $230 million from investors including OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, who is rumored to be developing an unrelated product (in collaboration with legendary Apple designer Jony Ive) that could better showcase AI’s promise."</item>
        <item>"Microsoft’s new Windows on Arm push is a milestone moment. It’s taken nearly five years to get to the point where the software maker is confident it has the upper hand over the MacBook Air on performance, battery life, and app compatibility.But behind the scenes, Microsoft has been working on something even bigger. While Microsoft has spent years working toward an Arm transition that will now play out throughout the summer and beyond, it’s the AI overhaul at the heart of this new generation of “Copilot Plus PCs” that could fundamentally change how we use Windows on a daily basis.
            \n I recently got the chance to hear from the leaders behind Microsoft’s big AI push, and they made it clear that this isn’t just a silicon change. Microsoft has rearchitected Windows 11 to run dozens of AI models in the background"</item>
        <item>"Sonos has vowed to restore those software functions in the weeks ahead, but the whole situation — and the unshakeable feeling that the app overhaul was rushed out the door — has rocked the trust between the audio brand and some of its most loyal customers. This is not where Sonos wanted to find itself in the lead-up to what CEO Patrick Spence has described as its most-requested new device ever.
            \n But it’s where we are now as the Ace headphones go up for preorder ahead of a June 5th release.Last week, the company hosted media in New York City for a first look at the Sonos Ace. I got to test out the noise-canceling headphones — not for long enough to form any serious judgments on sound quality — and experience their headline feature, which is the ability to instantly transfer TV audio from a Sonos soundbar to the headphones with the push of a button. The Ace headphones support spatial audio and head tracking, providing a cinematic private listening experience for those times when you might otherwise need quiet in the TV room. (Spatial audio can also be used during regular music listening."</item>
        <item>"Google only just rolled out AI summaries in search results — and now they’re getting ads. In an update on Tuesday, Google says it will soon start testing search and shopping ads within AI Overviews for users in the US.n the example shared by Google, the search engine’s AI overview lists a response to the question: “how do I get wrinkles out of clothes?”
            \n Beneath the AI-generated suggestions, there’s a new “Sponsored” section with a carousel showing wrinkle spray you can buy from places like Walmart and Instacart.Google says it will display ads in AI Overviews when “they’re relevant to both the query and the information in the AI Overview.” Advertisers that already run certain campaigns through Google will automatically become eligible to appear in AI Overviews. “As we move forward, we’ll continue to test and learn new formats, getting feedback from advertisers and the industry,” Google writes."</item>
        <item>"The trailer was executed very intelligently, showing snippets of the Kingdom Hearts games in chronological order, suggesting to potential customers (and reminding lapsed fans like me) in what order the games should be played. Steam will have three Kingdom Hearts games for sale: Kingdom Hearts -HD 1.5+2.5 ReMIX- (yes those dashes are officially part of the name), Kingdom Hearts HD 2.8 Final Chapter Prologue, and Kingdom Hearts III + Re Mind DLC. To make things easier, there will also be a bundle available, Kingdom Hearts Integrum Masterpiece, that combines all three games for one price.
            \n The trailer was executed very intelligently, showing snippets of the Kingdom Hearts games in chronological order, suggesting to potential customers (and reminding lapsed fans like me) in what order the games should be played. Steam will have three Kingdom Hearts games for sale: Kingdom Hearts -HD 1.5+2.5 ReMIX- (yes those dashes are officially part of the name), Kingdom Hearts HD 2.8 Final Chapter Prologue, and Kingdom Hearts III + Re Mind DLC. To make things easier, there will also be a bundle available, Kingdom Hearts Integrum Masterpiece, that combines all three games for one price.Those who purchase Kingdom Hearts III + Re Mind DLC will also get a special keyblade, “Dead of Night,” which looks pretty slick in Steam Logo blue and grey. Each of the three games is itself a bundle of a bunch of KH games spanning platforms and console generations. You can find a full breakdown of which game is in what bundle here or on each game’s Steam page."</item>
        <item>"Earlier today, Apple issued a fix in iOS and iPadOS 17.5.1. Patching buggy software is a good, normal thing. But that’s not the issue here. The issue is that the fix “addresses a rare issue where photos that experienced database corruption could reappear in the Photos library even if they were deleted” — and that’s all Apple has to say about it.
        \n This is obviously a privacy concern. It raises valid questions as to how Apple stores photo data and whether iPhone owners can truly trust that their deleted data is actually deleted. The Verge has reached out to Apple multiple times to comment publicly on the matter but has yet to receive a response. Doing so would at least shed light on why this bug happened, what’s been done to fix it, and what it’s doing to ensure that this won’t happen again. However, Apple has yet to respond."</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="img">
        <item>@drawable/humane</item>
        <item>@drawable/micro</item>
        <item>@drawable/sonos</item>
        <item>@drawable/google</item>
        <item>@drawable/king</item>
        <item>@drawable/apple</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>